Register of the Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction Miscellaneous Records, 1964-1972
Hoover Institution Archives
Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction Miscellaneous Records,
1964-1972
82042
Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction
18 manuscript boxes ( linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Minutes, agenda, and memoranda, relating to agriculture and rural development in Taiwan.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Biographical/Historical Note
American-Taiwanese development agency.
Scope and Content of Collection
Minutes, agenda, and memoranda, relating to agriculture and rural development in Taiwan.
Access Points
Agriculture--Taiwan.; Economic assistance, American--Taiwan.; Rural development--Taiwan.; Taiwan.; United States--Foreign relations.
Container List
- AGENDA AT JOINT COMMISSION ON RURAL RECONSTRUCTION (JCRR) MEETINGS, 1968-1972. (Box 1-14)
  Agenda discussed at JCRR meetings with background documentation filed chronologically by date of meeting.
  - 1968
    - July 26 (1775th meeting) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - August 2 (1776th meeting) (Folder 2)
    - August 5 (1777th meeting) (Folder 3)
    - August 9 (1778th meeting) (Folder 4)
    - August 12 (1779th meeting) (Folder 5)
    - August 16 (1780th meeting) (Folder 6)
    - August 19 (1781st meeting) (Folder 7)
    - August 23 (1782nd meeting) (Folder 8)
    - August 30 (1783rd meeting) (Folder 9)
    - September 6 (1784th meeting) (Folder 10)
    - September 9 (1785th meeting) (Folder 11)
    - September 13 (1786th meeting) (Folder 12)
    - September 16 (1787th meeting) (Folder 13)
    - September 20 (1788th meeting) (Folder 14)
    - October 25 (1795th meeting) (Folder 15)
    - October 28 (1796th meeting) (Folder 16)
    - November 1 (1797th meeting) (Folder 17)
    - November 12 (1798th meeting) (Folder 18)
    - November 18 (1799th meeting) (Folder 19)
    - November 21 (1800th meeting) (Folder 20)
    - November 25 & 29 (1801st meeting) (Folder 21)
    - December 2 & 6 (1802nd meeting) (Folder 22)
    - December 9 (1803rd meeting) (Folder 23)
    - December 20 (1804th meeting) (Folder 24)
    - December 23 (1806th meeting) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - December 27 (1807th meeting) (Folder 2)
  - 1969
    - January 6 & 10 (1809th & 1810th meetings) (Folder 3)
    - January 13, 17, 20 (1811-1813th meetings) (Folder 4)
    - January 27 (1814th meeting) (Folder 5)
    - February 3 (1816th meeting) (Folder 6)
    - February 6 (1817th meeting) (Folder 7)
    - February 10 & 14 (1818th & 1819th meetings) (Folder 8)
    - February 24 (1820th meeting) (Folder 9)
    - February 28 (1821st meeting) (Folder 10)
    - March 3, 7, 10 (1822-1824th meetings) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - March 14 (1825th meeting) (Folder 2)
    - March 17 (1826th meeting) (Folder 3)
    - March 21 (1827th meeting) (Folder 4)
    - March 24 (1828th meeting) (Folder 5)
    - March 26 (1829th meeting) (Folder 6-7)
    - April 6 (1830th meeting) (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - April 12 (1831st meeting) (Folder 3)
    - April 18 (1832nd meeting) (Folder 4)
    - May 2 (1834th meeting) (Folder 5)
    - May 12 (1835th meeting) (Folder 6)
    - May 16 (1836th meeting) (Folder 7)
    - May 19 (1837th meeting) (Folder 8)
    - May 23 (1838th meeting) (Folder 9)
    - May 26 (1839th meeting) (Folder 10)
    - June 6 (1841st meeting) (Folder 11)
    - June 9 (1842nd meeting) (Folder 12)
    - June 16 (1844th meeting) (Folder 13)
    - June 20 (1845th meeting) (Folder 14)
    - June 23 (1846th meeting) (Folder 15)
    - June 27 (1847th meeting) (Folder 16)
    - July 5 (1848th meeting) (Folder 17)
    - August 23 (1855th meeting) (Folder 18)
    - August 29 (1856th meeting) (Folder 19)
    - September 17 (1858th meeting) (Folder 20)
    - September 24 (1859th meeting) (Folder 21)
    - September 26 (1860th meeting) (Folder 22)
    - November 6 (1866th meeting) (Folder 23)
    - November 12 (1867th meeting) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - November 20 (1868th meeting) (Folder 2)
    - November 28 (1869th meeting) (Folder 3)
    - December 4 (1870th meeting) (Folder 4)
    - December 17 (1871st meeting) (Folder 5-6)
    - December 24 (1872nd meeting) (Folder 7)
    - December 31 (1873rd meeting) (Folder 8)
  - 1970
    - January 15 (1874th meeting) (Folder 9-10)
    - January 22 (1875th meeting) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - January 29 (1876th meeting) (Folder 2)
    - February 4 (1877th meeting) (Folder 3)
    - February 19 (1878th meeting) (Folder 4)
    - February 26 (1879th meeting) (Folder 5)
    - March 7 (1880th meeting) (Folder 6-7)
    - March 12 (1881st meeting) (Folder 8)
    - March 19 (1882nd meeting) (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - April 17, May 7, 21 (1886-1888th meetings) (Folder 3)
    - June 4, 18, 25 (1890-1892nd meetings) (Folder 4)
    - July 16 (1895th meeting) (Folder 5)
    - July 23 & 30 (1896th & 1897th meetings) (Folder 6)
    - August 13, 20, 27 (1899-1901st meetings) (Folder 7)
    - September 3 & 10 (1902nd & 1903rd meetings) (Folder 8)
    - November 25 (1913th meeting) (Folder 9)
    - December 4 & 10 (1914th & 1915th meetings) (Folder 10)
    - December 24 (1917th meeting) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - December 31 (1918th meeting) (Folder 2)
  - 1971
    - January 7 (1919th meeting) (Folder 3)
    - January 18 (1920th meeting) (Folder 4-5)
    - February 6 (1921st meeting) (Folder 6-7)
    - February 9 (1922nd meeting) (Folder 8)
    - February 18 (1923rd meeting) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - March 4 (1924th meeting) (Folder 2-3)
    - March 11 (1925th meeting) (Folder 4)
    - April 22, 29; May 6, 13, 24, 28 (1931-1936th meetings) (Folder 5)
    - June 10 & 17 (1937th & 1938th meetings) (Folder 6)
    - June 24 & July 8 (1939th & 1940th meetings) (Folder 7)
    - July 21 & 31 (1941st & 1942nd meetings) (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - August 5, 12, 19 (1943-1945th meetings) (Folder 2)
    - August 26 (1946th meeting) (Folder 3)
    - September 2 (1947th meeting) (Folder 4)
    - September 9 & 16 (1948th & 1949th meetings) (Folder 5)
    - October 15 (1951st meeting) (Folder 6)
    - November 6 (1952nd meeting) (Folder 7)
    - November 12 & 18 (1953rd and 1954th meetings) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - November 25 (1955th meeting) (Folder 2)
    - December 9 (1956th meeting) (Folder 3)
    - December 16 (1957th meeting) (Folder 4)
    - December 30 (1958th meeting) (Folder 5)
  - 1972
    - January 7 (1959th meeting) (Folder 6-7)
    - January 13 (1960th meeting) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - January 20 (1961st meeting) (Folder 2-3)
    - January 27 (1962nd meeting) (Folder 4)
    - February 3 (1963rd meeting) (Folder 5-6)
    - February 26 (1964th meeting) (Folder 7)
    - March 2 (1965th meeting) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - March 16 (1966th meeting) (Folder 2-3)
    - April 6 (1969th meeting) (Folder 4)
    - April 13 & 27 (1970th & 1971st meetings) (Folder 5)
    - May 11 & 25 (1972nd & 1973rd meetings) (Folder 6)
    - June 14 & 29 (1975th & 1976th meetings) (Folder 7)
    - July 7 & 13 (1977th & 1978th meetings) (Folder 8)
    - July 28 (1980th meeting) (Folder 9)
    - August 10 (1981st meeting) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - August 17 & 31 (1982nd & 1983rd meetings) (Folder 2)
- SUBJECT FILE, 1964-1972. (Box 14-18)
  Reports, minutes of meetings, studies, printed matter and other materials relating to activities of the JCRR in Taiwan.
  - Administrative Order No. 73 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural census, 1970 (Folder 4)
  - Agricultural Credit Program (Folder 5)
  - Agricultural Development Program, minutes of CIECO-MOEA-JCRR Conference on, August 20, 1968 (Folder 6)
  - Agricultural production growth rates, 1968-1970 (Folder 7)
  - Agriculture (Folder 8)
  - Asian Vegetable Development Center (Folder 9)
  - Brief statement on animal industry projects in Taiwan supported by JCRR, n.d. (Folder 10)
  - Chen, T. P., "Status and Problems of Acquaculture in Taiwan," reprint, Industry of Free China, March 1971 (Folder 11)
  - Chin, L. T., "Rotational Irrigation Development in Taiwan," June 30, 1968 (Folder 12)
  - Chinese Agricultural Technical Group to Vietnam, quarterly reports, 1970-71 (Folder 13)
  - Chinese language materials (Folder 14)
  - Chinese language materials (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
  - Committee on the Future of JCRR, minutes of meeting, September 19, 1969 (Folder 4)
  - Damm, J. K., Report on visits to India, Malaysia, Singapore, Hong Kong, Taiwan and Thailand, 23 April - 21 May 1967 (Folder 5)
  - "The Discipline of Soil and Water Conservation at Taiwan Provincial Chung-Hsing University, Taichung, Taiwan," n.d. (Folder 6)
  - English language publications (Folder 7)
  - Falcon, Walter P., "Key Issues in Taiwan's Agricultural Development - A Summary of the Seminar," December 1973 (Folder 8)
  - Family planning and population studies (Folder 9-10)
  - Farmer's Association in Taiwan (Folder 11)
  - Fisheries Division (Folder 12)
  - Forests and forestry (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Hendry, James B., The Small World of Khanh Han, 1964 (Folder 2)
  - Houlung Reservoir (Ming-teh) and Irrigation Project (Folder 3)
  - Hsu, S. C.
    - "Major Achievements of Health Program of Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction in 20 Years," 1968 (Folder 4)
    - "Nutrition Improvement Program," November 13, 1969 (Folder 5)
    - "Progress of Cooperative Projects in Medicine," 1968 (Folder 6)
  - Johnston, J. E., Report on Far East Tour, 1964 (Folder 7)
  - Joint Conference between Taiwan Provincial Government and JCRR, November 15, 1968 (Folder 8)
  - Land Reform Training Institute (Folder 9)
  - Levine, Gilbert, Report to the Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction Irrigation and Engineering, n.d. (Folder 10)
  - Library (Folder 11)
  - Loan program, FY 1967-69 (Folder 12)
  - Luh, C. L. and David Yen, Report on the Current Agricultural Condition in Guam and Suggested Plans for Agricultural Development, February 18, 1972 (Folder 13)
  - Minutes of meetings
    - 1968 (Folder 14)
    - 1969
      - January-May (Folder 15)
      - August-December (Folder 16)
    - 1970
      - January-July (Folder 17)
      - August-December (Folder 18)
    - 1971
      - January-May (Folder 19)
      - June-December (Folder 20)
    - 1972 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Ohio State University and the JCRR, research notes on agricultural formation and technological change (Folder 2)
  - Operational JCRR Program and Budget for FY 1969 (Folder 3)
  - Plant Industry Division
    - Huang, Cheng-hwa
      - "Rice Varietal Improvement in Taiwan," April 1969 (Folder 4)
      - The Second Rice Research Conference, April 28 - May 2, 1969 (Folder 5)
    - Liu, Ho-yuan (Folder 6)
    - Mushroom Research Program (Folder 7)
    - Peng, Tien-song, "The Development of Mechanized Rice Culture in Taiwan," June 1969 (Folder 8)
    - "Thinking and Doing for Better Crop Production - PID Activities," July 1968 - June 1969 (Folder 9)
    - Wang, Shin-tuan, "Briefing on Detailed Soil Survey of Cropland in Taiwan," n.d. (Folder 10)
  - Program for the visit of Truong Thai Ton, Minister of Agriculture and Agrarian Reform, Republic of Vietnam, and party to the Republic of China, September 21-28, 1968 (Folder 11)
  - Rural Economics Division
    - Publication List of Agricultural Economic Research, April 1971 (Folder 12)
    - "Rice Review," 1968-1970 (Folder 13)
  - Rural Health Division (Folder 14)
  - Shen, T. H.
    - "Future Prospects of Agrucultural Program Under the Fifth Four-Year Economic Development Plan," August 1968 (Folder 15)
    - "The Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction, Taiwan, Republic of China - A Summary," n.d. (Folder 16)
  - Staff meetings
    - 1968 (Folder 17)
    - 1969 (Folder 18)
    - 1970 (Folder 19)
    - 1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 1972 (Folder 2)
  - Sun, Y. P., "A Review of Current Research on Insect Control," n.d. (Folder 3)
  - Taiwan Agricultural Research Institute (Folder 4)
  - Taiwan East Asia Office Field Reports
    - 1970 (Folder 5)
    - 1970-72 (Folder 6)
  - United Nations Development Program, Food & Agriculture Organization, Soil & Water Conservation Study & Recommendation, "Development of Livestock Production on Marginal Land in Taiwan, Republic of China," 1965-66 (Folder 7)
  - United Nations Development Programme (Special Fund), Plan of Operation, n.d. (Folder 8)
  - Wilcox, F. R., "Report on My Observations in Taiwan," March 25, 1966 (Folder 9)
  - World Food Program for Forest and Rural Road Development in Taiwan, project proposal, February 1, 1970 (Folder 10)
  - Yuan, Po-wei
    - "The First Session of the Indo-Pacific Fisheries Council (IPFC) Special Committee on Management of Indo-Pacific Tuna FAO Headquarters, Rome, 21-23 April 1971," May 1971 (Folder 11)
    - Progress of Study on Marine Biology in the Republic of China, July 1970 (Folder 12)
    - Report on Participation in the Fourth Meeting of the International Coordination Group for the Cooperative Study of the Kuroshio Current and Adjacent Regions, July 1970 (Folder 13)
    - Report on the Fifth Meeting of the International Coordination Group for the Cooperative Study of the Kuroshio Current and Adjacent Regions and Symposium on the Results of CSK, June 1968 (Folder 14)
    - Report on the Seventh Meeting of the International Coordination Group for the Cooperative Study of the Kuroshio Current and Adjacent Regions and the Second Symposium on the Results of CSK, October 1970 (Folder 15)
    - Report on the Sixth Meeting of UNESCO, Inter-governmental Oceanographic Commission and International Group for the Cooperative Study of the Kuroshio Current, November 1969 (Folder 16)
  - Yuan, Po-wei and Ron-tszong Yang, "Taiwan Fisheries Today," n.d. (Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 18)